Hello friends, my name is Ashwini Kumar.
As friends, you all know that
brother, I already
work here in ICICI Bank.  Brother, the topic that is going to be
discussed here in today's video is
this.  If friends, a
course has been launched from the ICI site here.  Well friends,
they have a
tie up with NEET here.  NEET has
launched its own course.  Through which,
friends, if you complete that course here, then
brother, the job you get here is
100%, friends, they get you a job here
in ICICI Bank.  Friends, here that
course is of 21 days.
Your live classes continue for 21 days.  And brother,
whatever your salary etc. is in it, friends, I am going to
discuss it here in today's video,
how, so friends, you have to
enroll in it here.  How much will
your fee be here?
Brother, if you do this course then
what post are you going to get?  And brother,
what is your work going to be here?  Is
this the course that is going to be conducted?  Is this an
operations course or is this a sales course
?  Friends, here I am going to give
you complete information regarding this in today's video.
Brother, I have received many
DDMs and brother,
I have also received many personal messages that
brother, please tell us about a course by doing which
we
can directly get a job in ICICI Bank because brother, I am already
here in ICICI Bank.  So brother, in today's
video, I am going to tell you the complete details about
how
you can get a job directly in ICICI Bank as a
Relationship Manager.
Friends, here they have clearly written
that friends,
you can get a job directly in ICICI Bank
if you
complete this 21-day course.
Friends, this course is completed from the NIT site.
Your live classes will be held there only.
Friends, you will be
given the certificate right there.  I am going to tell you the complete information
step by step in today's video.
If you are
new to this channel then friends, please subscribe to the channel here.  If you like the
video then
friends, please like the video here
because brother,
you will keep getting such helpful content here.
Friends, let me tell you one more update.  If
you want to work as a Sales Officer in HDFC Bank,
friends.  Brother, if you
want to go to the post of on roll in HDFC Bank, then
brother, we have hiring.
We have vacancies etc. right now.   There are
vacancies at many locations right now.  If you have a
requirement here, if brother, you
want to get a job here in the post of Sales Officer in HDFC Bank,
then friends, the
link of the WhatsApp group is given below.  You
go and join.  What will happen with that is that
we will get your number.  You can
message us personally that we
want a job here in HDFC Bank, then we will
share the details with you and
you friends can come here after giving the interview,
if you get selected, it
depends on you.  Rest of the friends, the
link is given below, you
can try it here once.  Rest of the friends, let's
start the video here.
Friends, we are talking about relationship
management which has been typed from the NIT site of
ICICI Bank.
One course launched from NIT site
is PGDMR.  Ok?  I have done a
course for that which is a 21 day
course here.  Rest I will also show you here by turning
on the screen recording of my mobile.
Ok?  Brother, I have turned on the
recording on my mobile.
Here friends, as you can see on the screen.  It is
clearly written here that
friends, this course is completed from the NIT site.
Your course is going to be of 21 days.
What they have told you here is that brother, you are going to have a
fixed salary here.  More than 500
people have been deployed here so far.  And brother, the
most important point of this course is that brother,
if you do not have any experience.  If
you are a fresher then friends,
you are eligible for this course here.  And brother,
your classes are going to be live here.
You will be given certificates etc. here
from NIT side.  And friends, if we
talk about qualification here, then brother,
you should have completed your graduation.
You should have more than 50% marks here.
Friends, here your age
criteria should be between 21 years to
28 years.  100%
in 30 days, friends, here these
NIT people get you a job in ICICI Bank because
brother, they have a tie up here.  And brother, what are
its fees etc. going to be here?
I will take you to its website to learn how to enroll.
Friends,
his fixed salary here is going to be Rs
2.85 lakh per annum.  That
means, your in-hand salary will be ₹
19 to ₹00 here.
Brother, if after doing
this course you get a job in ICICI Bank, then
other friends,
I have opened its website here directly from NEET.
Brothers, friends, the
fee for this course here is going to be ₹42,000.  It
is a 21 day course and friends, if you complete it, then
after 21 days, you will get a job
directly in ICICI Bank.
Friends, if we talk about its fees here, then
brother, its fees are going to be ₹42,000.
If brother, you are not able to deposit its fee of ₹42,000 at one go, then
brother,
you can deposit it in installments or
you can also deposit its fee in loan here.
You
can also deposit its fees in installments.  The only thing is
that you will have to
pay a little extra money here.
Friends, you have to pay ₹10,000 as deposit here
and first of all you have to
pay ₹10,000.  As soon as your
test etc. is completed here, as soon as
your course starts,
you have to pay ₹10,000 here to book the seat.
You should
see that brother.  All the details are
given here.  Brother, you should go to its website here.
I will give the link below for the rest.
Friends, by going there, you
can easily check out
this course by clicking on its link here.  Brother, many people
are confused whether after doing this course, we will get a
position here?  Will we
get a relationship post?  Will we
get the bank operations job role here or will we get to see something else here.
First of all friends, you have to
know that if you
complete this 21 day course, then
you should know that
I have told you what your salary will be here.  ₹
19 to ₹00
will come in your account in hand and friends, after that,
your post here will be about
relationship management.  That
means whatever your work is, it will either be
put into home loan
or mortgage or
credit card.  That means
you will have to do the sales yourself.
Your work is going to be in the field.  That means the
feed will not be 100%.  In this you also have
some bank work to do.  Whatever your
feed work is, you have to
come to the bank and sort it out.
You may get a home loan.  You may get a mortgage.
You can get LAP and
brother you can get credit card department.
You will be
given work here related to sales of any of these.  He
is not a relationship manager.  It is relationship management.
You see, read it carefully here.  Whenever
you complete this course here for ₹42,000.  There is
a post graduate course here by doing diploma,
on completing which you
get a diploma, that is, you are
given a certificate and through that
you get directly selected on the roll of ICICI Bank,
friends.
Brother, if you do its PO course here, then
after doing the PO course, the
post of Relationship Manager is directly given to you here.  Its fee is ₹
2 to ₹5 lakh and the
time period is one year.  In that,
you have to
go to Manipal Academy within 1 year.  You have to go to Manipal
University here in Bangalore.
This course is a 21
day course.  You are going to have sales
work here.  If you are interested
then friends, please enroll in this course.
If brother, you do not want to do this course.  If
you want to go to the sales officer of HDFC Bank, then
brother, the link is given below.  It is
free of cost.  We will
not charge you a single penny.  We have only one book for
₹69.  If brother you
want to know about BFSC sector.  You want to improve your
resume here.
You want to know about the banking sector.  Do you
want to conduct an interview?  You have to see the interview questions.
What kind of interview questions are there?
So brother, we have a book on BFSI.
Here is the e-book.  I have a lunch here.
If brother you want to say goodbye to that.
Friends,
I am providing you all these things here for just ₹69.
I have given complete information about the BFSI sector here.
100% friends, whatever
experience I have here, I have
enrolled it here.  If brother, you
want to get it here, then
you can write e-book in the comment box
or friends,
you will get the WhatsApp number personally from me here.   Please
message me.  I will
provide you that book here.
If brother, you want to take it here then
you can try it here once.
We will also conduct the interview in HDFC Bank and
give it to you through the same book.  If
brother, you want to buy it and are interested, then
write e-book in the comment box below
and brother, please message me on WhatsApp here so that
you can get the book.
Rest of the friends, if you want to go here, please see.
If you also want to go to ICICI, then
brother,
you will have to waste ₹42 to ₹45,000 here.  I will
not say that it will be a waste, brother, you will have to spend money.
After that you will have sales
work.  What is better than that is that
we will provide it to you free of cost.
Ok?  The link is given below.
Go and join or send us a
message on WhatsApp.  Rest of the friends,
I have told you whatever
I have said here regarding the course.
I hope
you liked this information very much.  If you like the video
then please like it.  Brother, if
you have not yet subscribed to this channel, then
brother, please come quickly and subscribe to this channel.
See you
in the next video.  Till then take care.